

🛘 +90 539 340 5527 | 🔀 molcaytercanli@gmail.com | 🍪 www.tercanli.com | 🖸 molcay | 🤡 molcay | 📓 molcay | 🛅 molcay | 🐚 molcay

## Summary .

I'm a Software Engineer mostly focused on Python at EPAM Systems Poland. I have 4+ years experience specialising in the full stack web development, and I have experience on different cloud providers like Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Goggle Cloud Platform (GCP). I love \*nix based environments and enjoys to customise all of the development cycle and automating stuffs. Also, I interested in devising a better problem-solving methods for challenging tasks and learning new technologies.

### Skills

**Programming** Python, JavaScript, Java, Scala

**Web** Django, Vue.js, React, Play, Flask, Spring **Others** Docker, GCP, AWS, Bash, Jenkins

Languages Turkish, English

# **Work Experience**

**EPAM System**Kraków, POLAND

SOFTWARE ENGINEER November 2021 - Present

• Worked for a HR and Workforce Management Solution company

• Contributed a team develops a chatbot for the companies various products

Tech stack: aiohttp (Python), Socket.io for Python (WebSocket), Docker

• Contributed a team develops a tool to manage HR tasks

Tech stack: Django (Python), Docker

**Urla Digital Agriculture** 

Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

June 2020 - October 2021

Developed a software for IoT devices that automate the controlled-environment agriculture
 Tech stack: Python, Docker, Amazon Web Services (like Lambda, RDS, SQS, SNS, DynamoDB, CloudWatch, S3, SES, Timestream, Kinesis Firebose)

• Developed a dashboard to configure, update, and control IoT devices remotely

Tech stack: Django (Python), MySQL, SQLite, Docker

**Linovi** Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER December 2017 - June 2020

Developed and maintained web services that serve as a chat bots (Jira, Asana, GitHub, Zendesk, Salesforce, Pagerduty) for Google Chat
 Tech stack: Play (Scala), React (Javascript), MySQL, Redis, Jenkins, Google Cloud Platform (like AppEngine, Compute Engine, Cloud Pub/Sub, Stackdriver)

• Developed a dashboard for an autonomous driving software company

**Tech stack:** Vert.x (Java), React (JavaScript), Amazon Web Services

• Contributed a Software as a Service called Asena for an information security firm

**Tech stack:** Spring (Java), Angular.js (JavaScript), Flask (Python), Redmine

### Education & Certificates

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University

Muğla, TURKEY

COMPUTER ENGINEERING *GPA*: 3.52 / 4.00 September 2012 - June 2017

### **CERTIFICATES**

2017, Jan CCNA R&S: Routing and Switching Essentials, Cisco Networking Academy

2016, Jan CCNA R&S: Introduction to Networks, Cisco Networking Academy

2015, Dec Introduction to Cybersecurity, Cisco Networking Academy

APRIL 20, 2022 OLCAY TERCANLI · RÉSUMÉ